ERIC TAYLOR

302 NW Dogwood Ave; Redmond, Oregon, 97756; (541)639-5456; erictaylormx@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE:

Seeking a career as a Software Developer with YOUR AWESOME COMPANY. Ambitious with the drive to succeed in any situation. Experience in HTML, CSS and an understanding of Bootstrap. Additional experience with Python, SQLite and JavaScript. Five years' experience as a supervisor and look forward to new challenges, whatever the situation. Work well with others and efficiently on my own.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, SQLite, Python, Data Visualization, Google Docs, Microsoft Office Suite

EDUCATION:

B.S. in Computer Science, Mobile and Web Software Development, Anticipated Graduation: June 2022 *Oregon State University - Cascades*, Bend, OR

Basic Police Officer Certificate of Completion, Graduation: March 2017

Oregon Police Academy, Department of Public Safety Standards and Training, Salem, OR

Associate of General Studies, Graduation: June 2013 Central Oregon Community College, Bend, OR

Obtained Private Pilot Certification—Helicopter

RELATED COURSES:

Name of Course, Name of Course

EXPERIENCE:

Police Officer, Warm Springs Police Department, Warms Springs, OR, 2016 - 2018

- Solved urgent problems decisively and respond in emergency situations
- Accessed, navigated and updated complex database system
- Operated and required to troubleshoot body camera and patrol vehicle technical equipment
- Communicated effectively with upper management and diverse populations of people
- Worked cooperatively and efficiently as a team and individually
- Investigated and responded to thousands of accidents, thefts, disturbances, discrepancies
- Wrote hundreds of detailed, concise reports for prosecution
- Trained and supervised three police officers; instructed and tested on policy and procedures

Plant Manager, Straw Propeller Gourmet Foods, Redmond, OR, 2014 - 2016

- Initiated project to develop equations and link Excel spreadsheets to increase efficiency of inventory control, supply ordering and waste management
- Supervised the flow of supplies throughout the United States
- Managed ten employees and plant maintenance; created policies, procedures, and training standards

Financial Representative, Country Financial, Bend, OR, 2013 - 2014

- Kept information confidential while building relationships with clients to help them achieve financial security
- Communicated effectively in all situations and with a variety of clients

Area Supervisor, Air Force, Texas U.S.A., North Dakota U.S.A., Germany, 2004 - 2010

- Supervised patrols while controlling access to over \$500M in U.S. resources
- Trained, worked with and knowledgeable with several technical alarm systems
- Regularly passed individual inspections, unit inspections and Air Force wide inspections

ACTIVITES:

Member, *Tech Club,* OSU-Cascades, Bend, OR, September 2018 - Present **Member,** *Student Veterans Association,* OSU-Cascades, Bend, OR, September 2018 - Present **Volunteer,** *American Red Cross,* Bitburg, Germany, 2009 - 2010